A Finding Aid to the Ivan C. Karp Papers and OK Harris Works of Art Gallery Records, 1960-2014, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Artist Files, 1967-2014; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 34 Linear feet Boxes 4-38, 80
  - Past, Group C, 1968-2012; 4.6; Archival Resource Key
    - Dworkowitz, Alan, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 71)
    - Eckstein, Berry Morton, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 72)
    - Eisenstein, Avi, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 73)
    - Edwards, Benjamin, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 74)
    - Erró, 1976-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 75)
    - Escher, Fred, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 76)
    - Evans, Bruce, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 77)
    - Evans, Laura, 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 78)
    - Everett, Bruce, 1970s-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 79)
    - Eversley, Frederick J., 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 80)
    - Fagg, Rebecca, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 81)
    - Falsetta, Vincent, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 82)
    - Farber, Manny, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 83)
    - Finneran, William, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 84)
    - Fiorda, Daniel, 2000-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 85)
    - Fischer, R. M., 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 86)
    - Fish, Tom, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 87)
    - Flinn, Robert, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 88)
    - Ford, Francis, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 89)
    - Fox, Carson, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 90)
    - Frank, Richard, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 91)
    - Gabrielese, Peter, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Galles, Arie A., 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Geiger, Steven, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Gniewek, Robert, 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Goldstein, Jack, 1972-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Goldstein, Phil, 2000-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Grigorovich, Vladimir, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Gunther, Perry, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Hall, D. J., 1980s-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Ham, YounJoo, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Hamada, Hiroyuki, 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Han, H. N., 1972-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 12-15)
    - Hansen, Glen, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Havard, James, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Hebert, Tom, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Hendrix, Susan, 1999-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Herbert, George, 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Herfield, Phyllis, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Herman, Alan, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Heyer, Mark Jay, 1996-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Heyman, Abigail, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Hoelscher, Jason, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Hoffman, Martin, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Hofmekler, Ori, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Holcomb, Susan, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Horelick, Lauren Anne, 2002-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Horn, Gerald, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Hoschler, Richard, 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Hrycun, George, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Hyman, Sylvia, 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Inoue, Kazuko, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Ikawawa, Naoki, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Jacobs, Jim, 1976-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Jacobson, Gary, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - James, Nathan J., 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Jano-Zenou, Jack, 1995-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 39-40)
    - Jeffrey, Carlin, 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Jelinek, David, 1997-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - Jiminez, Luis, 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 43-45)
    - Jin, Ik-Song, 1998-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 46)
    - Johnston, Matthew, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 47)
    - Joseph, Richard, 1983-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 48)
    - Joyce, David, 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 49)
    - Judelson, David, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 50)
    - Kalina, Richard, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 51)
    - Kazlov, Brian, 1974-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 52)
    - Kearns, Jerry, 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 53)
    - Keith, Kit, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 54)
    - Kelly, Jay, 1993-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 55)
    - Kelly, Patrick, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 56)
    - Kerlin, Sherry, 1983-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 57)
    - Kerr, Ed, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 58)
    - Kiki, John, 2000-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 59)
    - Kilcullen, Robert, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 60)
    - King, Tony, 1987-1994; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 USB flashdrive (Box 36, Folder 61)
    - Kipniss, Robert, 1991-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 62)
    - Knafo, Hai, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 63)
    - Kogge, Robert, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 64)
    - Kosianski, Leonard, 2007-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 65)
    - Kreuger, Jack, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 66)
    - Kubina, Jerzy, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 67)
    - Kudo, Guty, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 68)
    - Kuhr, Alexis, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 69)
    - Kustura, Ivan, 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 70)
    - Larsen, Steen Valde, 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 71)
    - Laury, Micha, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 72)
    - Ledy, Ann, 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 73)
    - Lee, Unju, 1978-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 74)
    - Leigh, Harry, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 75)
    - Lentsch, Edward, 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 76)
    - Levinson, Mon, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 77)
    - Lew, Jeffrey, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 78)
    - Lew, Leslie, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 79)
    - Lewellyn, Don, 1972-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 80)
    - Li-Lan, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 81)
    - Lim, Choong-Sup, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 82)
    - Linden, Steve, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 83)
    - Linder, Tracy, 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 84)
    - Lindlof, Ed, 1996-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 85)
    - Lipski, Donald, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 86)
    - Littell, Ross, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 87)
    - Lomas, Raffael, 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Lowe, Robert, 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Lutzke, Richard, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Mabe, Joni, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - MacAdam, Jon, 2007-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Macauley, Thomas, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Mahaffey, Noel, 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Mahima, Akiko, 2008-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Manley, Bryn, 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Maresca, Joseph, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Marx, Amy, 2008-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Mastracco, Vincent, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Maxwell, Dwayne, 1987-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Mayercak, Zdeno, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Mazziotti, Mary M., 2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Menchiari, Roberto, 1994-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Mercer, Sunni, 1997-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Mihanesteanu, Lucian, 1999-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Mikus, Eleanore, 1997-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Milgrim, Charlene, 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Miller, Elliot, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Miller, Marc, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Minotto, Paul, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Moore, G. E., 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Morais, Edmund, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Moran, Pat, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Morley, Malcom, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Motyka, Jo, 2005-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Munding, Michael, 1994-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Murphy, J. Francis, 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Nagano, Yoko, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Nakagawa, Naoto, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Navarra, Douglas, 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Neumuth, Mary, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Nitka, Louis, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - Noble, Daniel, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - Noguchi, Tokuo, 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Novak, Lorie, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - Nowlin, Oliver, 1980s-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - O'Brien, Dennis, 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - Olson, Tim, 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - Opocensky, Pavel, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - Orselli, Janet, 2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - Ossi, James M., 1981-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - Oz, Avital, 1981-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 45)
    - Palaia, Franc, 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - Paschoal, Len T., 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 47)
    - Patrick, Joseph Alexander, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 48)
    - Perelman, Luis, 1969-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 49)
    - Pettibone, Richard, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 50)
    - Peugh, R. Benton, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 51)
    - Pföstl, Herbert A., 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 52)
    - Piacentino, Gianni, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 53)
    - Piedilato, Andy, 2001-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 54)
    - Poindexter, Ethel, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 55)
    - Posen, Stephen, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 56)
    - Pratt, Vernon, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 57)
    - Rabinowitz, Royden, 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 58)
    - Ravitz, Mark, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 59)
    - Ray, Linda, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 60)
    - Reed, Carl A., 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 61)
    - Reiback, Earl, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 62)
    - Rennels, Sig, 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 63)
    - Richardson, Judy, 1996-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 64)
    - Richert, Clark, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 65)
    - Ries, Wanda, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 66)
    - Rodriguez, Victor, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 67)
    - Rogers, Pamala, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 68)
    - Rogers, William, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 69)
    - Roje, Arsen, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 70)
    - Rosenberg, Edo, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 71)
    - Rosenfield, Leonard, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 72)
    - Roth, Cora H., 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 73)
    - Roth, Frank, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 74)
    - Roth, Richard, 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 75)
    - Rowan, Carol, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 76)
    - Rubin, Jeffrey, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 77)
    - Rubins, Nancy, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 78)
    - Rudich, Richard, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 79)
    - Ruiz, Denis William (Wintersong), 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 80)
    - Russell, Jeff, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 81)
    - Salfas, Dianne, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 82)
    - Sandman, Jo, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 83)
    - Sato, Masami, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 84)
    - Savage, W. Lee, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 85)
    - Schneir, Leonard, 1994-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 86)
    - Schwartz, Buky, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 87)
    - Schwartz, Eric, 1974-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 88)
    - Scott, Arden, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 89)
    - Senza, Gabrielle, 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 90)
    - Shaffer, Mary, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 91)
    - Shanbhag, Lei Zhang, 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 92)
    - Shaw, Karen, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 93)
    - Shedletsky, Stuart, 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 94)
    - Shimooka, Takafumi, 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 95)
    - Siler, Todd, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 96)
    - Silver, Steve, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 97)
    - Sinclair, Maryellen, 1991-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 98)
    - Smith, Lawson, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 99)
    - Smith, Richard, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 100-101)
    - Soffer, Sasson, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 102)
    - Soghor, William, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 103)
    - Sonmor, Kevin, 1994-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 104)
    - Souza, Al, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 105)
    - Stamm, Ted, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 106)
    - Steihauer, Andrew, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 107)
    - Stever, Jorge, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 108)
    - Stewart, William, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Stickloon, R. G., 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Stone, Cynthia, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Stratford, Herb, 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Sunseri, Don, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Suska, Cestmir, 1997-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Taylor, Richard, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Thorne, Patrick, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Tobin, Steve, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Troy, Richard, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Tzannes, George, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Ursachi, Leonard, 1989-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Valenta, Barbara, 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Venet, Bernar, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Victoria, Ted, 1974-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Von Ringelheim, Paul, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Wald, Carol, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Weber, Eleanore, 1997-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Weber, Idelle, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Weinstein, Jeffrey S., 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Weir, Margi, 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Weller, Ted, 2002-2007; Archival Resource Key; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Wheeler, Mary, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Wholley, Jay N., 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Wideman, Robert, 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Willis, Thornton, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Wohl, Robin, 1995-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Wojcik, Gary, 1975-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Wolfe, Gerald, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Woodburn, Stephen B., 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Wulke, Joy, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Wurtzel, Daniel, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Yalovitz-Blankenship, Maxine, 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Young, John T., 1991-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Zaig, David, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Zenkius, Jerry, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Zhang, Naijun, 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 37)
- Printed Material, 1963-2014; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; 5.2 Linear feet Boxes 38-44, 80, OV 88-OV 90
  Printed material produced by OK Harris Works of Art includes a complete set of exhibition announcements. Scattered among the announcements are a small number of invitations to gallery events including receptions, openings, a sock hop, a few performances, concerts, and parties. Although OK Harris presented as many as six concurrent exhibitions every six weeks, the number of exhibition catalogs and posters is very small, reflecting the tight schedule. Earlier printed material is particularly creative and unique, each announcement carving out an attention getting and occasionally humorous approach, some with modest shock value. The graphics are usually interesting as are the materials used. Over time, OK Harris's printed items became more traditional with postcard style announcements predominating.
  Printed material produced by others consists of periodicals, books, exibition catalogs, guidebooks and clippings. Most are about or mention Ivan Karp, Marilyn Karp, gallery artists and exhibitions. Exhibition catalogs feature works by OK Harris artists and works loaned by the gallery; also included are catalogs of shows for which Karp was a juror. Miscellaneous items relate to events with Karp as a speaker or juror. Scattered throughout is general information about SoHo and Photo-realism. Exhibition Posters are: "Amerikanske Realister," Randers Kunstmuseum; "Ivan C. Karp Photographs," California State University, Long Beach; "Los Angeles Heute," Amerika Haus; and "Ivan Karp: The Face of Contemporary Art," Hong Kong Institute for Promotion of Chinese Culture. Miscellaneous posters are: "Walt Disney" by W. Fawcett, "Marihuana" (sic), "Artist being Booked for Exhibiting Without Talent," "Biscuits" by Manuel Hughes, and "Davis Cone."
  Additional printed items generated by OK Harris Works of Art and other sources are found among administrative files (Series 2), artists' files (Series 3), and the Ivan C. Karp papers (Series 8).
  This series is arranged as 2 subseries:
  5.1: Produced by OK Harris Works of Art, 1969-2014
  5.2: Produced by Others, 1963-2012
  - Produced by OK Harris Works of Art, 1969-2014; 5.1; Archival Resource Key
    - Exhibition Schedules, 1969-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Exhibition Announcements, 1969 October-1981 July; Archival Resource Key; Oversized material housed in Box 80 (Box 38, Folder 39-50)
    - Exhibition Announcements, 1981 September-1992 July; Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 1-11)
    - Exhibition Announcements, 1992 September-2003 September; Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 1-11)
    - Exhibition Announcements, 2003 September-2014 April; Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 1-11)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, 1974-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 12-13)
    - Exhibition Posters, 1972-1990; undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 14)
      Oversized material housed in OV 88
    - Oversized Exhibition Announcements from Box 38, Folder 39), 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 80)
    - Oversized Exhibition Posters from Box 41, Folder 14, undated; 1972-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 88)
  - Produced by Others, 1963-2013; 5.2; Archival Resource Key
    - Articles, undated; 1963-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 1-15)
    - Books, 1985-2010; undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 16-20)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, 1963-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 1-15)
    - Invitations to September 11 Memorial Exhibitions, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Printed Items, 1975-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 17-19)
    - Periodicals, 1972-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 20-21)
    - Oversized Exhibition Posters, 1973-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 89)
    - Oversized Posters, Miscellaneous, undated; 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 90)
- Artwork, 1970s-circa 1980s; Series 6; Archival Resource Key; 0.8 Linear feet Box 44, OV 81-OV 87
  This series consists of 40 prints by OK Harris artists. With the exception of two black and white prints, all are color lithographs. Radical Realism I is a set of six signed and numbered prints (an edition of 200) by John Clem Clarke, Richard Estes, Ralph Goings, Richard McLean, Malcolm Morley, and John Salt issued by Mother Lode Editions in 1972. Other color lithographs are by John Baeder, Robert Bechtle, Davis Cone, Ralph Goings, Randy Green, H. N. Han, John Kacere, Richard McLean, Naoto Nakagawa, and John Salt; one bears an illegible signature.
  Correspondence (Series 1) includes small drawings and other artwork enclosed with a number of number of artists' letters to Ivan and Marilynn Karp, a variety of hand made holiday cards, and some illustrated letters. A small amount of artwork also is scattered among the artists' files (Series 4).
  - Oversized Black and White Prints by Douglas Bond and Roger A. Bultot, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 81)
  - Oversized Color Lithographs, Radical Realism I, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 81)
  - Oversized Color Lithographs, Bader - Bechtle, undated; 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 82)
  - Oversized Color Lithographs, Cone, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 83)
  - Oversized Color Lithographs, Goings, 1970s-circa 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 84)
  - Oversized Lithographs, Green - Nakagawa, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 85)
  - Oversized Color Lithographs, Kacere, 1977; undated; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 86)
  - Oversized Color Lithographs, Salt - Unidentified, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 87)
- Photographic Materials, 1960s-2014; bulk 1969-1999; Series 7; Archival Resource Key; 32 Linear feet Boxes 44-76